goalvideoz.com 2012-12-05

# GoalVideoz - Advertisement Request

## PRIVACY POLICY

Privacy Policy

The following webpage outlines Goalvideoz.com's collection and use of personal information from it's users. Goalvideoz.com values the privacy of our members and users, we will never share any personal information of anybody who logs on to Goalvideoz.com with anyone. This includes your e-mail address, name, and location. Upon logging on to Goalvideoz.com such things as your IP address and hostname are logged for statistical and security reasons. 

Cookies A cookie is a very small text file placed on your system upon logging on to Goalvideoz.com (and most other websites). This file serves as your identification card and is uniquely yours, and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Cookies tell us that you have returned to a specific web page on Goalvideoz.com and help us track your preferences and transactional habits. The basic function of cookies is to help our server remember who you are. 

**Children's Privacy**  
Goalvideoz.com does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 13. We make reasonable efforts to prevent someone who is underage from joining as a member of Goalvideoz.com, and will not collect information from them. If Goalvideoz.com learns that a child under the age of 13 has become a member, we will close that child's account and delete any information collected about the child. Not withstanding the foregoing, Goalvideoz.com may choose to retain some personal information such as the child's e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering at our website. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) went into effect in April 2000, and as a result websites all over the world wide web had to change their standards to not collect any information from a child. 

**Disclosing Information**  
Goalvideoz.com may store and disclose personal information allowed or required by applicable law or when deemed advisable by us. This means that we may make disclosures that are necessary to conform to legal and regulatory requirements or processes and to protect the rights, safety, and property of Goalvideoz.com, users of the Goalvideoz.com website, and the public. 

**Security**  
At Goalvideoz.com we make reasonable efforts to protect personal information such as passwords and use technology such as encryption, access control procedures, firewalls, and physical security. We urge you to use a unique password with both letters and numbers to protect your account on Goalvideoz.com and it's affiliated websites. If others, including family, friends or other household members access and use the message board through your login credentials, you are responsible for the actions of that individual. Only in extreme cases will your account be fully terminated. 

**Third Parties**  
Third Party websites may collect information from users of Goalvideoz.com, this information will include your IP address, hostname, and information about your system to help us serve you better. These are purely used for statistical reasons, and will not be used in any way other then that. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org

**Website Policy Changes**  
Goalvideoz.com reserves the right to change this, and any other policy located on our website at anytime without notifying our users. If you have any comments, questions, or concerns regarding this policy, please feel free to contact [william@springmobility.com](mailto:william@springmobility.com) with the topic as privacy policy 

By continuing to access Goalvideoz.com and any of it's affiliated websites and files, you are expressly and impliedly agreeing to all of the terms as stated above on this document. You also hereby affirm that you are in compliance with all Federal, State and Local laws in your place of residence concerning the contents of Goalvideoz.com.

| 

#### Football Videos by Category

#### Top Players

|  | 

**Cristiano Ronaldo**

 **Man Utd**  
the superior player of red devils, he is Cristiano Ronaldo playing for Manchester United.  
Cristiano Ronaldo Videos

| 

#1  
  
---|---|---  
  
 | 

**Ronaldinho**

 **Barcelona**  
He's known as the best of the world, Ronaldinho Gaucho playing at Barcelona.  
Ronaldinho Videos

| 

#2  
  
---|---|---  
  
 | 

**Kaka**

 **Milan**  
One of the most skilled players in the world, Golden Ball winner, he is Kaka playing for A.C Milan.  
Kaka Videos

| 

#3  
  
---|---|---  
  
#### Latest Discussion on Forums

#### More GoalVideoz

#### Sponsored Links
